<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevSecOps Studio</title>
    <link>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DevSecOps Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dso-studio.teachera.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Dependencies DevSecOps Studio uses vagrant, virtualbox and ansible to setup the lab environment. You can visit the vendor&amp;rsquo;s website to download the above software for on Windows/Linux/macOS.
DevSecOps Studio simulates the environment presented below.
Software  Vagrant Virtualbox Ansible  Hardware  Atleast 4GB of RAM for the virtual machines. 60GB of HDD Space. Intel i3 Processor or above.  MacOS Installation Prerequisites can also be installed via homebrew on MAC OS X</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools Used</title>
      <link>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/tools/</guid>
      <description> What&amp;rsquo;s included in the environment? The environment contains the following tools used in different stages of DevSecOps.
Detailed tool list    Technology Tools     PenTest Toolkit: Nmap, Metasploit   Static Analysis Tools: Brakeman, bandit, findbugs   Dynamic Analysis Tools: ZAP proxy, Gaunlt   Hardening: DevSec Ansible OS Hardening   Compliance: Inspec   Operating System : Ubuntu Xenial (16.04)   Programming Languages: Java, Python 2, Python 3, Ruby/Rails   Container Technology: Docker   Source Code Management: Gitlab (github like system)   CI Server: Gitlab CI/Jenkins   Configuration Management: Ansible   Monitoring and Log management: Elastic Search, LogStash and Kibana   Cloud Provider Utilities: AWS CLI   Utilities: Git, Vim, curl, wget,    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap &amp; Changelog</title>
      <link>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Quo vadis?
Todo Features Provision the stack on AWS using vagrant. Build Images using Packer and upload to vagrant cloud. Add Container scanning using clair.  Contributing Did you found an bug or you would like to suggest a new feature? I&amp;rsquo;m open for feedback.
Please open a new issue and let me know.
You&amp;rsquo;re also welcome to contribute with pull requests.
Need Human ? If you have any questions regarding this repo, please contact Mohammed A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dso-studio.teachera.io/license/</guid>
      <description>Copyright &amp;copy; 2018 Mohammed A. Imran @secfigo Copyright &amp;copy; 2018 Raghunath G @raseyon
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>